Guide to the School of Medicine, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Vernon W. Lippard, 1936-1976; Accession 1979-A-007
  - XIII. VARIOUS MEDICAL COMMITTEES CORRESPONDENCE, 1951-1967
    - Program for the Development of Medical. Students, 1962 (Box 109, Folder 29)
    - Publication of Yale School of Medicine, 1964-1965 (Box 109, Folder 30)
    - Regional Medical Program, Committee on, 1965-1966 (Box 109, Folder 31)
    - Stistica1 Services, Central, 1961-1963 (Box 109, Folder 32)
    - Stockroom, central, 1958 (Box 109, Folder 33)
    - Student Affairs, Committee on, 1951-1964 (Box 109, Folder 34)
    - Thesis, Committee on, 1963 (Box 109, Folder 35)
    - Yale School of Nursing, Report of the President's Committee, 1955 (Box 109, Folder 36)
  - XIV. MEDICAL STUDY UNITS: CORRESPONDENCE, 1939-1960
    - Arthritis Study Unit, 1955-1957 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Cardiovascular Study Unit, 1946-1952 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - General, 1953-1960 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Poliomyelitis Study Unit, 1939-1961 (Box 110, Folder 4 - 8)
    - Psychiarty and Law Study Unit, 1952-1956 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Rehabilitation Study Unit, 1952-1957 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - XV. YALE UNIVERSITY CORRESPONDENCE WITH VARIOUS OFFICES AND ORGANIZATIONS, 1950-1964
    - Accident Prevention Director, 1960-1964 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Administration: Comptroller's office tax exemption memorandum, 1957 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Administration: Presidents' office, 1954-1963 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Administration: Provost's office, Kingman Brewster Jr., 1961-1963 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Administration: Recording Secretary, 1959-1965 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Administration: Treasurer's office, George Gage, 1955-1964 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Administration: Veterans Affairs, Selective Service, Foreign Nationals, Foreign Study Program, 1952-1955 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Air Raid Committee, 1962 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Alcoholic Studies, Center of, 1955-1964 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Bishop Museum, The, 1951 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Business Management, Department of: A.C. conversion at the medical school, 1961-1962 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Commencement programs, 1956-1962 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Director of Information: Carlos F. Stoddard, Jr., 1958-1962 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Episcopal Church at Yale, 1954-1957 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Faculty of Arts and Sciences: Science Advisory Committee, 1953-1959 (Box 111, Folder 15 - 16)
    - Forestry, School of, 1954 (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - History, Department of, 1959 (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Housing Bureau, 1953-1962 (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Human Relations, Institute of: Claude Buxton, 1959-1960 (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - International office, 1964-1966 (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Isotope Committee, 1954-1965 (Box 112, Folder 22)
    - Law School, 1961 (Box 112, Folder 23)
    - Liaison Committee between the Faculty Club and the university, 1954-1961 (Box 112, Folder 24)
    - Maintenance: Lewis Beach, 1953-1963 (Box 112, Folder 25)
    - Maintenance and construction: E.J. Behler, 1953-1959 (Box 112, Folder 26)
    - Molecular Biology, Ad Hoc Panel on, 1961 (Box 112, Folder 27)
    - Pastoral Ministry, Committee on, 1959 (Box 112, Folder 28)
    - Patents, Committee on, 1953-1964 (Box 112, Folder 29)
    - President's Committee to Choose Dean, 1966-1967 (Box 112, Folder 30)
    - Psychology, Department of, 1953-1964 (Box 112, Folder 31)
    - Purchases, Bureau of, 1953-1964 (Box 112, Folder 32)
    - Religion and Medicine, Committee on: Lectures on Medical Ethics, 196'2-1965 (Box 113, Folder 33)
    - Sociology, Department of, 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 34)
    - Sterling Hall of Medicine, Ad Hoc Committee on Plans for, 1963-1964 (Box 113, Folder 35)
    - Student Cap and Gown Agency, 1956-1959 (Box 113, Folder 36)
    - Student Research, Department of: Lists for money to cover expenses, 1958-1961 (Box 113, Folder 37)
    - Students: fellowship announcements, 1959-1962 (Box 113, Folder 38)
    - Students: results of fellowship applications, 1956-1963 (Box 113, Folder 39)
    - Sub-Personnel: Blue Cross, Social Security, 1953 (Box 113, Folder 40)
    - University Council, 1955-1963 (Box 113, Folder 41)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1963-1964 (Box 113, Folder 42)
    - Yale Corporation: general, 1962-1964 (Box 113, Folder 43)
    - Yale Corporation: minutes, 1950-1964 (Box 113, Folder 44 - 46)
    - Yale Reports Radio Programs, 1963 (Box 113, Folder 47)
  - XVI. 1980 ADDITION: ADMINISTRATIVE FILES, 1946-1976
    - Allied Health Personnel, Program for, 1969-1970 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Fund, 1968-1971 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 1952-1967 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Applachian Regional Center for the Healing, Arts, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Appointments and Salaries, Records of, 1946-1964 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Articles written by Vernon W. Lippard: reprints, 1936-1960 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Biology and Medicine- Incorporated, Yale Journal of, 1970-1976 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Cleveland State University, 1967-196/ (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Connecticut Regional Medical Program, 1967-1968 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: miscellaneous and personal, 1948-1969 (Box 115, Folder 11 - 15)
    - Correspondence: miscellaneous and personal, 1970-1979 (Box 116, Folder 16 - 18)
    - Correspondence on arrival of V.W. Lippard at Yale, 1952-1953 (Box 116, Folder 19 - 22)
    - Cost Study Program, 1966-1968 (Box 117, Folder 23)
    - Curriculum revision, 1966 (Box 117, Folder 24 - 25)
    - Curriculum study, 1953-1968 (Box 117, Folder 26 - 27)
    - Curriculum vitae, 1937-1938 (Box 117, Folder 28)
    - Development- Office of, 1967-1968 (Box 117, Folder 29)
    - Education, 1961-1963 (Box 117, Folder 30)
    - Education, Graduate: Report of The Task Force on, 1973-1974 (Box 117, Folder 31 - 32)
    - Epidemiology and Public Health, Reorganization of Department of, 1958-1960 (Box 118, Folder 33 - 36)
    - Faculty Salary Study, 1964-1967 (Box 118, Folder 37)
    - Financial Aid to Medical Education, 1949-1952 (Box 118, Folder 38 - 39)
    - Financial Aid to Medical Education, 1949-1952 (Box 119, Folder 40 - 41)
    - Half Century of American Medical Education 1920-1970: Vernon W. Lippard, 1975 (Box 119, Folder 42)
    - Health Service, University: Advisory Committee on Medical Planning, 1967-1968 (Box 119, Folder 43 - 44)
    - Health Service, University: Search Committee for Director of, 1969 (Box 119, Folder 45 - 46)
    - Laboratory of Surgery, Obstetrics and Gynocology, 1967-1970 (Box 119, Folder 47)
    - Liaison Committee on Medical Education, 1976 (Box 120, Folder 48)
    - National Board Examiner, 1968-1975 (Box 120, Folder 50)
    - National Fund for Medical Education, 1971-1979 (Box 120, Folder 51 - 52)
    - Nursing, School of: President's Committee, 1955 (Box 120, Folder 53)
    - Pan American Federation of Associations of Medical Schools, 1968-1971 (Box 120, Folder 54)
    - Pediatrics: Grover F. Powers Professorship, 1968-1973 (Box 120, Folder 55)
    - Philippines, 1968-1969 (Box 120, Folder 56)
    - Pittsburgh, University of: Board of Visitors, 1968-1972 (Box 120, Folder 57)
    - Psychiatric Institute, 1977 (Box 120, Folder 58)
    - Saginaw Valley Study, 1968-1972 (Box 120, Folder 60)
    - South Carolina Advisory Commission on Higher Education, 1967-1968 (Box 121, Folder 61)
    - Speechs to groups outside of Yale, 1947-1972 (Box 121, Folder 62 - 65)
    - Stanford University Education, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 66)
    - Talks for alumni meetings, 1953-1958 (Box 121, Folder 67)
    - Talks for alumni meetings, 1959-1965 (Box 122, Folder 68)
    - Talks for dedications, 1955-1966 (Box 122, Folder 69)
    - Talks for faculty, 1952-1966 (Box 122, Folder 70)
    - Talks for students, 1953-1967 (Box 122, Folder 71)
    - Tennessee Higher Education Commission, 1970-1971 (Box 122, Folder 72)
    - Time and Scope Options, Study Group in, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 73)
    - U.S. News and World Report: interview with V.W. Lippard, 1958 (Box 122, Folder 74)
    - World Health Organization, 1967 (Box 122, Folder 75)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine: "Cancer Research at Yale", 1957 (Box 122, Folder 76)
    - Yale-New Haven Hospital, 1969-1976 (Box 122, Folder 77)
    - Yale-New Haven Medical Center, Development of, 1966 (Box 122, Folder 78)
- Records, 1952-1976; Accession 1981-A-026
  Restricted until January 1, 2051
  - Anesthesiology, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Behavioral Sciences Study Center, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Behavioral Sciences Study Center, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Biochemistry, Department of, 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Biochemistry, Department of: Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry Proposal with Yale College, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Biochemistry, Department of: Department of Molecular Construction, 1953-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Biochemistry, Department of: Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry alterations, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Biochemistry, Department of: Biochemistry/Biophysics merger, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Cell Biology, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chaplaincy Program, 1962-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Child Study Center, 1962-1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Clinical Facility Study Group, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Clinical Facility Study Group: Interim Report, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Committee: Atypical Growth, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Committee: Cancer Research Program, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Committee: Children's Clinical Research, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Committee: Primary Care, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Committee: Progress, 1952-1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Computer Sciences, Section of, 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Computer Sciences, Section of, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Dermatology, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health, Department of, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health, Department of, 1960-1968 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Epidemiology and Public. Health, Department of: Ostfield, Adrian M., 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health, Department of: Research Center Grant Application, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Governance, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Governance, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Governance: Notes on Participation in the Governance of Yale University Parts I-IV, [1969?] (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Health Evaluation Program, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Health Evaluation Program: Final Report, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 31 - 32)
  - Health Science Resources, 1969-1974 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Health Science Resources, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - History of Science and Medicine, 1961-1968 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - History of Science and Medicine, 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - History of Science and Medicine: The Making of a Library. Cushing, Harvet; Klebs, Arnold C.: Fulton, John F., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Human Genetics, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Internal Medicine, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Internal Medicine, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Internal Medicine: Cardiology Section, 1968-1972,1974 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - International and Area Studies, Programs in: Reports for the Year, 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - International Health, Committee 'on, 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - International Health, Committee on, 1965-1968 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - International-Health Program, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - International Health-Program: Africa, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - International Health Program: Central and West Africa Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - International Health Program: East Africa, 1968-1972 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - International Program: Carribean Consortium, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - International Program: Central and South America, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - International Program: Vietnam, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Neurology, 1963-1973 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Nursing, School of, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Nursing, School of., 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1967-1973 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology: Abortion Clinic, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology: Budget and Space Information, 1954-1966 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology: Ford Foundation, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology: Sex Counseling Service, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Ophthamology, Department of, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Patient Care Study Center, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Patient Care Study Center, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Pathology, Department of, 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Pathology, Department of, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Pathology, Department of: Anatomical Pathology and Cytopathology, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Pediatrics, Department of, 1970-1974 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Pediatrics, Department of, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Pharmacology, Department of, 1967-1973 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Physicians Associate Program: Allied Health, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Physicians Associate Program: Committee on Education of Allied Health Personnel, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Physicians Associate Program, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Physicians Associate Program, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Physiology, Department of, 1969-1973 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - President, Office of the, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - President, Office of the, 1963-1968 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Provost, Office of the, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Psychiatry, Department of, 1969-1973 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Psychiatry, Department of, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Psychiatry, Department of: Annual Report: Psychosomatic Consultation-Liaison Service, 1973 July - 1974 June (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Psychiatry, Department of: Track Material, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Radiology, Department of, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Radiology, Department of, 1963-1968 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Radiology, Department of: Construction, 1958-1966 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Radiology, Department of: Diagnostic Radiology, 1968-1973 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Radiology, Department of: Space, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Radiology, Department of: Therapeutic Radiology, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Surgery, Department of, 1967-1973 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Surgery, Department of: Section of Anesthesiology, 1967-1971 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Surgery, Department of: Section of Ophthalmology, 1967-1971 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Surgery, Department of: Surgical Associates Program, 1970 October 30 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Surgery, Department of: Trauma Program, 1969-1974 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Surgery, Department of: Trauma Program: Third Progress Report, 1974 June (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Surgery, Department of: Trauma Program: Second Progress Report, 1973 June (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Surgery, Department of: Trauma Program: First Progress Report, 1971 September (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Surgery, Department of: Trauma Program: Emergency Medical Communications System for Southern Central Connecticut, 1971 October (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - University Health, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - University Health, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - University Health: Advisory Committee on Medical Planning, 1965-1969 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - University Health: Advisory Committee on Medical Planning: Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - University Health, Board of, 1967-1973 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - University Health, Board of, 1952-1966 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - University Health, Department of, 1954-1966 (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - University Health: Search-Committee for Director of University Health Services, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Yale-New Haven Medical Center, 1962-1970 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Yale-New Haven Medical Center: Family Health Care Project, 1965-1967 (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Yale-New Haven Medical Center: Hospital Bed Tower, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - Yale-New Haven Medical Center: Housing and Community Development, 1967-1972 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Yale-New Haven Medical Center: Joint Adninistrative Committee, 1970-1975 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Yale-New Haven Medical Center: Joint Administrative Committee, 1963-1969 (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Yale-New Haven Medical Center: Joint Board, 1972-1975 (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Yale-New Haven Medical Center: Joint Board, 1965-1971 (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Yale-New Raven Medical Genter: Master Plan, 1961-1967 (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - Yale-New Haven Hedical Center: Memorial Unit Expansion Program, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 114)
- Records of Robert W. Berliner, 1962-1982; Accession 1984-A-017
  Restricted until January 1, 2020.
  - AAMC--Division of International Medical Education, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Red Cross (Board of Directors), 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Association of Yale Alumni, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Campaign for Yale, 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Campaign for Yale Medical School Faculty Gomm., 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cogen and Holt, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Connecticut Cancer Epidemiology Unit, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Committees--
    - Anatomy and Microbiology, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Associate Clinical Practioners, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Behavioral Sciences--Medical School, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Biochemistry in University, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Biomedical Sciences, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Black Faculty Members, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Canar, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Clinical Titles, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Community Health Program, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Conn. Regional Medical Program, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Gross Anatomy, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Legislative Policy, 196"9 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Medical Ethics, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Multidisciplinary Unit labs, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Organization of Clinical Practice, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Review Me/PhD Program, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Status of Sections, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 26 - 27)
    - Task Force Committee Graduate Education, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Committee Research Ranks and Titles, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Deanship, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Dr. Rice's Project, 1968- (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Organization Model (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Financial Affairs through 1978
    - Ernst and Ernst, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - McKinsey, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Peat, Manvick, Mitchell, and Co., 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Search for Director of Finance, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Health Manpower Legislation--AAMC Memos, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 41 - 42)
  - Health Manpower Legislation, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 43 - 44)
  - Health Manpower Legislation, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Health Manpower Legislation, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 46 - 47)
  - Health Manpower Legislation, 1977 January - September (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Health Manpower Legislation, 1977 January - September (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Health Manpower Legislation, 1977 September - 1978 June (Box 6, Folder 50 - 51)
  - Hospice, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 52 - 53)
  - Human Investigation Committee--Fetal Research, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Human Investigation Committee, 1963-1971 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Human Investigation Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - International Exchange Visit, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Joint Committee on Planning and Priorities, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Legal Matters--Selman vs. Harvard, et a1., 1979 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Neuroanatomist Search Committee (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Neuroanatomy, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Committee to establish Graduate program in Neuroscience, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - New England Deans Meeting, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Pilar Gyorrfy Report, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Planning and Priorities, 1972-1982 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Practice Income Sharing Plan, 1968-1972 (Box 9, Folder 68 - 69)
  - Incentive Statements before final revision, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Reproduction and Population Research Center, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Research Career Development, 1968-1977 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - SCOR(Specialized Center of Research), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Space and Parking, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Space and Parking, 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Space and Parking, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 76 - 77)
    - St. Johns Parking (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - State of Connecticut Health Planning Council, 1969-1974 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - U. S. Pharmacopeial Convention, Inc., 1969-1980 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - U. S. Pharmacopeial Convention, Inc., 1969-1980 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - University of Connecticut, 1970-1976 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - World Health Organization Reference Serum Bank, 1962-1982 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Yale and Community Physician Coordinating Comm., 1968-1979 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Yale New Haven Hospital, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Yale New Haven Hospital, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 87 - 88)
  - Yale New Haven Hospital, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Yale New Haven Hospital, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Yale New Haven Hospital, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Yale New Haven Hospital Building Program, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 92 - 93)
- Records of Leon Rosenberg and Robert Berliner, 1953-1987; Accession 1988-A-034
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  - Anesthesiology
    - 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Cell Biology
    - 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1967-1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1969-1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1967-1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Child Study CTV
    - 1969-1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Dedication-Child Study Center, 1977 September (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Comparative Medicine
    - 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 1978 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 1977 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - 1975 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - 1974 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Dermatology
    - 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - EPH
    - 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Marmor, Theodore Dep't of Epidemiology and Public Health, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Historical Overview of the Department (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - 1975 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 49 - 50)
    - 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - History of Medicine
    - 1977 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Internal Medicine
    - 1977 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - 1976 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - 1977 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - 1976 (Box 3, Folder 64)